Guide to the Native American Educational Services Community Board Training Project Records 1978-1995
University of Chicago Library
- Series VI: Publications, Media, and Public Relations
  - Evaluations and surveys, miscellaneous follow-up data from reports, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Evaluations and surveys, operational plan for evaluations, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Funding sites, Avon Products, Inc., report and correspondence, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Funding sites, Borg-Warner Foundation, correspondence and report, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Funding sites, Bowman Lingle Trust Foundation, correspondence and book entry, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Funding sites, Educational Foundation of America, correspondence and book entry, 1981-1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Funding sites, General Mills Foundation, correspondence and book entry, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Funding sites, Hearst Foundation, notes and contact information, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Funding sites, Russell Sage Foundation, book entry, correspondence, booklet, 1980-1983 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Funding sites, The Spencer Foundation, booklet, book entry, correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Funding sites, Sun-Times Charity Trust, correspondence and proposals, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Individuals, Hattie Clark, resume and correspondence, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Intercom, certificate of award for achievement in the Chicago Indian Community, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Job openings and posted positions, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Handbooks and manuals, financial and small business manuals, 1983-1986 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Handbooks and manuals, student and volunteer manuals, no date (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Handbooks and manuals, teacher manual, United States History, grade 7, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Media, articles and newspaper clippings on Native American social issues, 1980-1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Media, news releases, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Papers from seminars, 1979-1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Publications Committee, memos, meeting minutes, and audit, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Publications, The Adult Learning Center Newsletter, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Bulletin of the Clearinghouse on Teacher Education, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Center for Law and Education, Inc. Newsnotes, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Publications, The Chicago Reporter, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Clearinghouse for Community Based Free Standing Educational Institutions Newsletter, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Fort Belknap Camp Crier, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Publications, The Forum for Liberal Education, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Friends Committee on National Legislation Indian Report, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Indian Law Support Center Reporter, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Linkages for Indian Child Welfare Programs, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Publications, miscellaneous drafts and materials, 1979-1995 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Publications, Monthly Product Announcements, United States Department of Commerce, Bureau of the Census, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Publications, Muckleshoot Smoke Signals, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Publications, Native American Rights Fund Announcements, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Publications, The Networker, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Publications, New Directions in Indian Purpose – Reflections on the American Indian Chicago Conference, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Publications, North Central Association Today, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Publications, Oh-Yo, A Bulletin for American Indian-Alaska Native Women, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Publications, Oklahoma City Camp Crier, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Publications, Perspectives, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Publications, The Statement of the Case for NAES College – Building a Model for Higher Indian Education, no date (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Publications, A Summation of the Developmental Planning Stage, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Publications, Vietnam Era Veterans Inter-Tribal Association Newsletter, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Resources, human resources correspondence and materials, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Transparencies and presentation materials, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Series VII: Restricted
  Series VII contains student records from courses and seminars held by the Community Board Training Project which are restricted for 80 years. This series has been arranged alphabetically.
  - Courses, seminars, Community Board Training Project, Funding Systems, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous course records, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Student records, transcripts, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Series VIII: Oversized
  Series VIII contains two examples of letterhead designs for the Chicago American Indian Community Organization Conference.
  - Letterhead samples, no date (Box 17, Folder 1)